Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Henry Chauncey, Jr., concerning institutional research and the bicentennial, 1963-1977; Accession 1977-A-008
  - General Files
    - Shoe String Press, Inc., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 363)
    - Shutack (Peter) Memorial, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 364)
    - Shuttle Bus Information, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 365)
    - Sigma Xi, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 366)
    - Silliman College, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 367)
    - Singer Report, "A Bill of Obligations for Yale University", 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 368)
    - Southeast Asia Studies, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 370)
    - Southern Connecticut State College, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 371)
    - Space Allocation, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 372)
    - Space Meeting, 1971 May 7 (Box 18, Folder 373)
    - Stack family, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 374)
    - Statistics, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 375)
    - Ezra Stiles College, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 376)
    - Associated Student Agencies, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 377)
    - Students for a Democratic Society, 1969, undated (Box 18, Folder 379)
    - Student Records, 1969, undated. (Box 18, Folder 380)
    - Student Unrest, 1970, undated (Box 18, Folder 381)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 383)
    - Summer Programs, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 384)
    - Summer Programs, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 385)
    - Summer Programs, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 386)
    - Summer School of Music and Art, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 387)
    - Summer Stipends, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 388)
    - T - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 389)
    - Telephones, 1969-1972, undated (Box 19, Folder 392)
    - Town School Meeting, 1972 April 25 (Box 19, Folder 394)
    - Transitional Year Program, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 395)
    - Tuitions and Fees, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 397)
    - Deferred Tuition, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 398)
    - U - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 399)
    - Undergraduate Grades, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 400)
    - Undergraduate Housing, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 401)
    - Undergraduate Research, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 402)
    - Undergraduate Student Organizations, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 403)
    - Undergraduate Tuition and Pees, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 404)
    - Union Negotiations, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 405)
    - United Way, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 406)
    - University Council, Community Relations (Ranney), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 407)
    - University Council Meeting, 1972 December 1 (Box 19, Folder 408)
    - University Council Executive Committee, 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 409)
    - University Council - General, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 410)
    - University Council - Committee Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 411)
    - University Engagement Book, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 412)
    - University Facilities - General, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 413)
    - Unsell Project, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 414)
    - Urban Studies, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 415)
    - V - General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 416)
    - Vaill, George D., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 417)
    - Veterans Administration Benefits, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 418)
    - Vietnam Veterans against the War, 1972, undated (Box 20, Folder 419)
    - W - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 420)
    - Whitehall, 1970-1971, undated (Box 20, Folder 421)
    - Whitehall, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 422)
    - Wiggins and Dana (legal matters), 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 423)
    - Wolfers (Arnold) Professorship, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 424)
    - Women, Change of Name, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 425)
    - Women at Yale, Recruitment of, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 426)
    - Women's Center, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 427)
    - Wood Carvers, Yale, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 428)
    - Woodbridge Hall, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 429)
    - Woodbridge Hall Door, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 430)
    - Woolsey Hall, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 431)
    - Woolsey Hall War Memorial, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 432)
    - WTNH-TV, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 433)
    - WYBC, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 434)
    - X-Y-Z - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 435)
    - Xerox machine, Woodbridge Hall, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 436)
    - The Yale Batteries, Fairfax Downey, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 437)
    - Yale "Blue", 1972 (Box 21, Folder 438)
    - Yale Center for British Art and British Studies, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 439)
    - Yale College Deanship, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 440)
    - Yale College Faculty Committee, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 441)
    - Yale College Faculty Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 442)
    - Yale College Introductory Booklet, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 443)
    - Yale Daily News, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 444)
    - Yale Daily News: admissions articles, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 445)
    - Yale Daily News: coeducation articles, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 446)
    - Yale Film Associates, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 447)
    - Yale Literary Magazine, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 448)
    - Yale Men in Service (Classes of 1965-69), 1969 (Box 21, Folder 449)
    - Yale Name, Protection of, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 450)
    - Yale Non-Faculty Action, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 451)
    - Yale Organizations, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 452)
    - Yale Outdoor Recreational Center (Box 21, Folder 453)
    - Yale Publications, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 454)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 455)
    - Yale Seal, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 456)
    - Yale Symphony, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 457)
    - Yale Today Panel, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 458)
    - Yale University women's Organization, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 459)
    - YMCA, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Office of Institutional Research
    - Ad Hoc Research Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 461)
    - Institutional Research Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 462)
    - Admissions Research Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 463)
    - Research: Admissions, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 464)
    - Research: Admit-Withdraw Study, Class of 1975 Cross-filed Admissions, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 465)
    - Research: Children of Alumni of Undergraduate Schools, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 466)
    - American Consul on Education, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 467)
    - Educational Research Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 468)
    - Applicants for Jobs - Institutional Research, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 469)
    - Research - Athletes, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 470)
    - Institutional Research Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 471)
    - Research - Burnham Papers, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 472)
    - Research - CEEB Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 473)
    - SCrs IBM Course [Henry Chauncey], 1970 (Box 22, Folder 474)
    - Educational Research: College Board Scores, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 475)
    - Research: Criteria Study - General, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 476)
    - Research: Development Office, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 477)
    - Institutional Research, Enrollment Fall, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 478)
    - Research: Grades, Yale College, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 480)
    - Research: Graduate School - Economics, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 481)
    - Research: Grants for Research, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 482)
    - Research: John Hoskins
      - 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 483)
      - 1971 (Box 23, Folder 484)
      - 1970 (Box 23, Folder 485)
      - Interrelationship of CEEB Test Scores and Academic Performance in the Yale College Classes of 1973 and 1974 (Box 23, Folder 486)
    - Institutional Research, McClelland, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 487)
    - Institutional Research, Medical School, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 488)
    - Educational Research, miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 489)
    - Educational Research, miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 490)
    - Institutional Research Office Proposal, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 491)
    - Research: Postgraduate Plans, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 492)
    - Research Problems, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 493)
    - Research: Residential College Courses, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 494)
    - Research: Sports, Intercollegiate and Coaching, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 495)
    - Educational Research Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 496)
    - Robert Sternberg, Research Papers, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 497)
    - Robert Sternberg, Research Papers, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 498)
    - Robert Sternberg, Research Papers: Applicant Information Duplication, memorandum, typescript and AN, 1971 February 26 (Box 24, Folder 499)
    - Robert Sternberg, Research Project, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 500)
    - Research: Successful Undergraduate Study, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 501)
    - Research: Testing and Learning Committee, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 502)
    - Research: Undergraduate Admissions, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 503)
    - Educational Research: Undergraduate Grades, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 504)
    - Research: Undergraduate predictions, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 505)
    - Proposal for Research in Undergraduate Admissions, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 506)
    - Research: Undergraduate Admissions -School Groups, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 507)
    - Research: Women Faculty, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 508)
  - U.S. Bicentennial Events and Planning, 1971-1976 (Box 24, Folder 509)
    - New Haven Bicentennial Commission, Certificate of Contribution, undated (Box 25, Folder 510)
    - Soccer Cup, American Bicentennial, 1976, undated (Box 25, Folder 511)
    - Art Gallery - Bicentennial Commission '76, 1972-1976, undated (Box 25, Folder 512)
    - New Haven Bicentennial Commission
      - 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 513)
      - 1975 (Box 25, Folder 514)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 515)
- Annual reports, degree files, and indexes maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1900-1976; Accession 1978-A-008
  - Annual Reports
    - 1969-1970
      - Administrative Sciences, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - American Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Anatomy, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Anthropology, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Astronomy, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Athletics, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Biology, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Chemistry, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Child Study Center, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - City Planning, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Comparative Literature, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Computer Science, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Design and Planning, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Economics, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - English, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Far Eastern Languages, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Geology and Geophysics, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Germanic Languages, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - History, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - History of Art, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - History of Science and Medicine, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Mathematics, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Medieval Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Microbiology, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Military Science, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Music, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Ophthalmology, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Pathology, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Pediatrics, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Pharmacology, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Philosophy, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Physics, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Physiology, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Political Science, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Psychiatry, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Radiology, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Religious Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Romance Languages, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Sociology, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Surgery, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Endowment and Gifts Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Human Relations Area Files, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Physical Education, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Police Department, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Summer Language Institutes, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Summer School: Music and Art, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - Western Office, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - 1970-1971
      - Administrative Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Admissions, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Afro-American Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Anatomy, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Anthropology, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Astronomy, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Chemistry, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Child Study Center, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Design and Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - East and South Asian Languages and Literatures, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Economics, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - English, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Geology and Geophysics, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - History, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Internal Medicine, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Linguistics, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Mathematics, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Medieval Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Microbiology, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Music, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Pathology, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Pediatrics, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Pharmacology, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Physics, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Physiology, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Psychiatry, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Radiology, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Religious Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Romance Languages and Literatures, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Sociology, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
      - Surgery, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
    - 1971-1972
      - Administrative Science, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Architecture, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - Art, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - Afro-American Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - American Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - Admissions, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Anatomy, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Anesthesiology, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - Anthropology, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - Astronomy, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Behavioral Science, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Biology, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - Chemistry, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Child Study Center, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 30 - 31)
      - Child Study Center, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 32 - 33)
      - Dermatology, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - East Asian Languages and Literatures, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Economics, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - English, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - Education of Women, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - Geology and Geophysics, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - History, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - History of Art, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - History of Science and Medicine, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - Internal Medicine, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - International Office, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - Language Laboratory, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Language Institute, Summer, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - Laboratory Animal Sciences, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - Linguistics, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
      - Mathematics, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Medicine, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Medieval Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Microbiology, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Music, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Neurology, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Ophthalmology and Visual Science, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Pediatrics, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Pharmacology, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Philosophy, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Physics, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Physiology, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Police, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Psychiatry, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Psychology, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Radiology, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Regional Office, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Surgery, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Sociology, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Statistics, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
    - 1972-1973
      - Administrative Science, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Afro-American Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Alumni Placement Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - American Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Anatomy, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Anesthesiology, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Annual Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Anthropology, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Architecture, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Association of Yale Alumni, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Astronomy, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Babylonian Collection, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Behavioral Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Biology, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Branford College, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Chemistry, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Child Study Center, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Chubb Fellowship, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Co-education Report, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Yale College, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Comparative Literature, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Computer Science, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Curriculum on International and Area Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Council on African Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Council on Southeast Asian Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Dermatology, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - East Asian Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Economics, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - English, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Geology and Geophysics, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Health Service, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - History, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - History of Art, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - History of Science and Medicine, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Human Genetics, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Inter-college Athletics, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Italian Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Internal Medicine, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Language Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Linguistics, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Mathematics, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Medieval Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Microbiology, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Mid-career Program in City School Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Music, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Neurology, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Ophthalmology and Visual Science, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Outdoor Education Center, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Pathology, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Pediatrics, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Pharmacology, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Philosophy, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Physical Education, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Physics, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Physiology, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Police, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Political Science, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Psychiatry, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Psychology, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Radiology, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Research in the Economics of Higher Education, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Religious Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Romance Languages, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Russian and East European Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Sociology, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Summer Language Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Surgery, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - 1973-1974
      - Administrative Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 70)
      - Afro-American Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - American Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Anatomy, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Anesthesiology, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Anthropology, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 71)
      - Architecture, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Art Gallery, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 72)
      - Astronomy, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 73)
      - Athletics, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Behavioral Sciences Study Center, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 74)
      - Branford College, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Calhoun College, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Career Advisory Service, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Chemistry, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Comparative Literature, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Council on African Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Collection, African, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Council on East Asian Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Diagnostic Radiology, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 75)
      - Divinity School, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Drama School, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 76)
      - Education of Women, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Jonathan Edwards College, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - English, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Financial Aid, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 77)
      - Graduate School, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Health Services, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 78)
      - History of Art, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - History of Science and Medicine, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Language Laboratory, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Mathematics, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 79)
      - Medicine, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Medieval Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Microbiology, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Music, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 80)
      - Neurology, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Nursing, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Ophthalmology, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Peabody Museum, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 81)
      - Pharmacology, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 82)
      - Physical Education, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Physics, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Physiology, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Police, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 83)
      - Political Science, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Psychiatry, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Religious Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 84)
      - Saybrook College, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Silliman College, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Sociology, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Spanish and Portuguese, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Ezra Stiles College, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Surgery, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Therapeutic Radiology, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 85)
      - Undergraduate Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Yale Center for British Art, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - 1974-1975
      - Afro-American Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 86)
      - Anesthesiology, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Anthropology, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Architecture, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Art Gallery, 1974-1975 (Box 13)